<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item><i>Everything we do is practice for something greater than where we currently are. Practice only makes for improvement.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Les\u00A0Brown</item>
        <item><i>Practice like you\'ve never won. Perform like you\'ve never lost.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Michael\u00A0Jordan</item>
        <item><i>Practice like it means everything in the world to you. Perform like you don\'t give a damn.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Jascha\u00A0Heifetz</item>
        <item><i>The most perfect technique is that which is not noticed at all.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Pablo\u00A0Casals</item>
        <item><i>I think it\'s beautiful to practice. I love to practice.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Claudio\u00A0Arrau</item>
        <item><i>When I am playing, I am in ecstasy; that is what I live for.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Claudio\u00A0Arrau</item>
        <item><i>The art of interpretation is not to play what is written.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Pablo\u00A0Casals</item>
        <item><i>Making mistakes is not my enemy... fear of making mistakes is my enemy</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Anne\u00A0Shih</item>
        <item><i>Sweat more in practise, bleed less in war.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Spartan\u00A0Warrior\u00A0Credo</item>
        <item><i>Practice is the best of all instructors</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Publius\u00A0Syrus</item>
        <item><i>Great thoughts reduced to practice become great acts</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0William\u00A0Hazlitt</item>
        <item><i>You can\'t hire someone to practice for you.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0H. Jackson Brown, Jr.</item>
        <item><i>For the things we have to learn before we can do them, we learn by doing them.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Aristotle</item>
        <item><i>I don\'t know if I practiced more than anybody, but I sure practiced enough. I still wonder if somebody — somewhere — was practicing more than me.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Larry\u00A0Bird</item>
        <item><i>Sincere practice, makes the impossible possible.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Dada\u00A0Vaswani</item>
        <item><i>Champions keep playing until they get it right.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Billie\u00A0Jean\u00A0King</item>
        <item><i>You are what you practice most.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Richard\u00A0Carlson</item>
        <item><i>Don\'t get set into one form, adapt it and build your own, and let it grow, be like water.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Bruce\u00A0Lee</item>
        <item><i>Determination, effort, and practice are rewarded with success.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Mary\u00A0Lydon\u00A0Simonsen</item>
        <item><i>The greater danger for most of us lies not in setting our aim too high and falling short; but in setting our aim too low, and achieving our mark.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Michelangelo</item>
        <item><i>Practice without improvement is meaningless.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Chuck\u00A0Knox</item>
        <item><i>Tomorrow\'s victory is today\'s practice.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Chris\u00A0Bradford</item>
        <!--        <item><i>If you can play it slow, you can play it fast.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Musician\u00A0Truth</item>-->
        <item><i>Practice the way you want to perform. Practice as if you were performing.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Master\u00A0Advice</item>
        <item><i>If you don\'t believe you are the best, then you will never achieve all that you are capable of.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Cristiano\u00A0Ronaldo</item>
        <item><i>They say that nobody is perfect. Then they tell you practice makes perfect. I wish they\'d make up their minds.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Winston\u00A0Churchill</item>
        <item><i>To become really good at anything, you have to practice and repeat, practice and repeat, until the technique becomes intuitive.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Paulo\u00A0Coelho</item>
        <item><i>Persistence, persistence, and persistence. The power can be created and maintained through daily practice - continuous effort.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Bruce\u00A0Lee</item>
        <item><i>If you don\'t practice, you don\'t deserve to win.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Andre\u00A0Agassi</item>
        <item><i>Talent is a pursued interest. Anything that you\'re willing to practice, you can do.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Bob\u00A0Ross</item>
        <item><i>Practice like you\'ve never won. Play like you\'ve never lost.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Michael\u00A0Jordan</item>
        <item><i>Experts were once amateurs who kept practicing.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Amit\u00A0Kalantri</item>
        <item><i>I\'ve always considered myself to be just average talent and what I have is a ridiculous insane obsessiveness for practice and preparation.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Will\u00A0Smith</item>
        <item><i>I do not play this instrument so well as I should wish to, but I have always supposed that to be my own fault because I would not take the trouble of practicing.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Jane\u00A0Austen</item>
        <item><i>Practice makes permanent, not perfect. If you practice the wrong thing, you make the wrong act permanent.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Hamza\u00A0Yusuf</item>
        <item><i>You don\'t learn to walk by following rules. You learn by doing and falling over.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Richard\u00A0Branson</item>
        <item><i>Practice every time you get a chance.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Bill\u00A0Monroe</item>
        <item><i>Amateurs practice until they get it right, experts practice until they can\'t get it wrong.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Julie\u00A0Andrews</item>
        <item><i>You always have to be on edge. You always have to take every practice, every game, like it is your last.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Kobe\u00A0Bryant</item>
        <item><i>Knowledge is of no value unless you put it into practice.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Anton\u00A0Chekhov</item>
        <item><i>Sketching on a regular basis requires you to pay close attention to the visual world around you. With practice, you begin to see things you never noticed before.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Paul\u00A0Laseau</item>
        <item><i>In previous years I was so fired up at times I made little mistakes. So I kept telling myself to be patient, relax, play like you do in practice.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Randall\u00A0Cunningham</item>
        <item><i>You can practice shooting eight hours a day, but if your technique is wrong, then all you become is very good at shooting the wrong way. Get the fundamentals down and the level of everything you do will rise.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Michael\u00A0Jordan</item>
        <item><i>It is performance ready if you can play 7 times without error. If you mess up on the 6th run through, you have to start over.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Musician\u00A0Truth</item>
        <item><i>Talent without working hard is nothing.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Cristiano\u00A0Ronaldo</item>
        <item><i>Do or do not, there is no try.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Yoda</item>
        <item><i>It takes a long time to sound like yourself</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Miles\u00A0Davis</item>
        <item><i>Give me six hours to chop down a tree and I will spend the first four sharpening the ax.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Abraham\u00A0Lincoln</item>
        <item><i>The goal of practice is always to keep our beginner\'s mind.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Jack\u00A0Kornfield</item>
        <item><i>If you think you can or you think you can\'t, you\'re right.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Henry\u00A0Ford</item>
        <item><i>Practice does not make perfect. Only perfect practice makes perfect.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Vince\u00A0Lombardi</item>
        <item><i>Hard work beats talent when talent doesn\'t work hard.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Unknown</item>
        <item><i>I\'m a strong believer that you practice like you play, little things make big things happen.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Tony\u00A0Dorsett</item>
        <!--        <item><i>“Almost right” is “wrong.”</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Musician\u00A0Truth</item>-->
        <item><i>I am one of those who will go on doing till all doings are at an end.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Wolfgang\u00A0Amadeus\u00A0Mozart</item>
        <item><i>The better voice doesn\'t mean being a better singer.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Luciano\u00A0Pavarotti</item>
        <item><i>The rivalry is with ourself. I try to be better than is possible. I fight against myself, not against the other.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Luciano\u00A0Pavarotti</item>
        <item><i>If I don\'t practice one day, I know it; two days, the critics know it; three days, the public knows it.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Jascha\u00A0Heifetz</item>
        <item><i>The most important thing to do is really listen.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Itzhak\u00A0Perlman</item>
        <item><i>Passion is one great force that unleashes creativity, because if you\'re passionate about something, then you\'re more willing to take risks.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Yo-Yo Ma</item>
        <item><i>A wrong note played with the right intention is much to be preferred to the right note played with no soul.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Janine\u00A0Jansen</item>
        <item><i>If you\'re playing within your capability, what\'s the point? If you\'re not pushing your own technique to its own limits with the risk that it might just crumble at any moment, then you\'re not really doing your job.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Nigel\u00A0Kennedy</item>
        <item><i>My dear hands. Farewell, my poor hands.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Sergei\u00A0Rachmaninov</item>
        <item><i>Simplicity is the highest goal, achievable when you have overcome all difficulties.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Frederic\u00A0Chopin</item>
        <item><i>To play without passion is inexcusable!</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Ludwig\u00A0van\u00A0Beeethoven</item>
        <item><i>An artist is someone who has learned to trust in himself.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Ludwig\u00A0van\u00A0Beethoven</item>
        <item><i>Play always as if in the presence of a master.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Robert\u00A0Schumann</item>
        <item><i>You have to put in the hours because there\'s always something which you can improve.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Roger\u00A0Federer</item>
        <item><i>Good ideas are not adopted automatically. They must be driven into practice with courageous patience.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Hyman\u00A0Rickover</item>
        <item><i>If I thought of gymnastics as a job, it would put too much stress on me ... At the end of the day, if I can say I had fun, it was a good day.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Simone\u00A0Biles</item>
        <item><i>You can\'t jump from little things to big things. It just takes time and patience.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Nadia\u00A0Comaneci</item>
        <item><i>It\'s very hard to get to the top. It\'s hardest to stay at the top.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Nadia\u00A0Comaneci</item>
        <item><i>I want to be able to look back and say, I\'ve done everything I can, and I was successful.\' I don\'t want to look back and say I should have done this or that.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Michael\u00A0Phelps</item>
        <item><i>I think goals should never be easy. They should force you to work, even if they are uncomfortable at the time.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Michael\u00A0Phelps</item>
        <item><i>If you want to be the best, you have to do things that other people aren\'t willing to do.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Michael\u00A0Phelps</item>
        <item><i>You can\'t put a limit on anything. The more you dream, the farther you get.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Michael\u00A0Phelps</item>
        <item><i>Tough times don\'t last — tough people do!</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Dan\u00A0Peña</item>
        <item><i>Don\'t just work longer hours, \'staying busy\' as most other people do. \'Work smart\' i.e. Stay productive and don\'t get distracted.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Dan\u00A0Peña</item>
        <item><i>Just doing as well as you did last time is not good enough.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Michael\u00A0Jackson</item>
        <item><i>Practice means to perform, over and over again in the face of all obstacles, some act of vision, of faith, of desire. Practice is a means of inviting the perfection desired.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Martha\u00A0Graham</item>
        <item><i>The greatest education in the world is watching the masters at work.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Michael\u00A0Jackson</item>
        <item><i>Do not go to bed until you have gone over the day three times in your mind. What wrong did I do? What good did I accomplish? What did I forget to do?</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Pythagoras</item>
        <item><i>Knowledge is not skill.  Knowledge plus ten thousand times is skill.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Sinichi\u00A0Suzuki</item>
        <item><i>If you spend too much time thinking about a thing, you will never get it done.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Bruce\u00A0Lee</item>
        <item><i>Your mind must get there before your fingers will.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Musicians\u00A0Truth</item>
        <item><i>One thing I have learned is that I\'m not the owner of my talent; I\'m the manager of it.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Madonna</item>
        <item><i>Write down specific measurable goals, and check them off as you achieve them.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Master\u00A0advice</item>
        <item><i>If you practice correctly from the beginning, you will save yourself a lot of time and frustration later on. Don\'t practice bad habits!</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Master\u00A0advice</item>
        <item><i>Find a way to make your practice routine exciting! And when it isn\'t exciting anymore, change up the routine.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Master\u00A0advice</item>
        <item><i>No matter how you feel, get up, dress up, show up, and practice.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Master\u00A0advice</item>
        <item><i>When you are not practising, someone else is getting better.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Allen\u00A0Iverson</item>
        <item><i>Arriving at one goal is the starting point to another.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0John\u00A0Dewey</item>
        <item><i>Setting goals is the first step in turning the invisible into the visible.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Tony\u00A0Robbins</item>
        <!--        <item><i>Watch your posture!</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Master\u00A0advice</item>-->
        <!--        <item><i>Maybe this is the wrong fingering...</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Musician\u00A0Truth</item>-->
        <item><i>I fear not the man who has practiced 10,000 kicks once, but I fear the man who has practiced one kick 10,000 times.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Bruce\u00A0Lee</item>
        <item><i>Use only that which works, and take it from any place you can find it.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Bruce\u00A0Lee</item>
        <item><i>If I wanted to play the violin, I had to work. Because anything that one wants to do really, and one loves doing, one must do everyday. It should be as easy to the artist and as natural as flying is to a bird. And you can\'t imagine a bird saying well, I\'m tired today, I\'m not going to fly!</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Yehudi\u00A0Menuhin</item>
        <item><i>One must always practice slowly. If you learn something slowly, you forget it slowly.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Itzhak\u00A0Perlman</item>
        <item><i>Quick music sounds dull unless every note is articulated.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Herbert\u00A0von\u00A0Karajan</item>
        <item><i>It is only through failure and through experiment that we learn and grow.</i>\u0020\u0020-\u00A0Isaac\u00A0Stern</item>
        <!--        <item><i>Keep working - one day it will happen!</i></item>-->
        <item><i>I can\'t do it... YET</i></item>
        <!--        <item><i>It isn\'t hard, it\'s new. Practice makes it not new.</i></item>-->
        <!--        <item><i>Do you want to be the one who makes us sound worse?</i></item>-->
    </string-array>
</resources>
